Finding Aid for the Medical Artifacts Collection
Eskind Biomedical Library Manuscripts Collection
- Box 101 1229 Symonds Picture-Story Test. Symonds Picture-Story Test. New York: Bureau of Publications, Teachers College, Columbia University, 1948. Twenty psycho-diagnostic plates. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 101 1230 Bellak, Leopold, and Bellak, Sonya Sorel. Children’s Appreciation Test (C.A.T.). Seventh printing, third and revised edition. New York: C.P.S. Co., 1959. Ten psycho-diagnostic plates. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 101 1231 Bellak, Leopold, and Bellak, Sonya Sorel. Senior Appreciation Technique (S.A.T.). Larchmont, New York: C.P.S. Inc., 1973. Sixteen diagnostic plates and manual. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 101 1232 Blum, Gerald. The Blacky Pictures. New York: The Psychological Corporation, 1950. Twelve psycho-diagnostic plates. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 101 1233 The Michigan Picture Test. The Michigan Picture Test. Chicago: Science Research Associates, Inc., 1953. Sixteen psycho-diagnostic plates. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 101 1234 Sines, J.O., and Parker, J. D. Missouri Children’s Picture Series. 1964. Approximately 240 cards. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 101 1235 Psycho-Diagnostic Puzzles Two picture puzzles of prints of paintings by Jessie Wilcox Smith entitled: “Playing Mother” and “Off to Play Stutsman”. Printed by Sterling Company, Chicago. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 102 1236 Pictorial Completion Test Illustrated by Marguerite Davis. Published and manufactured by Stoelting Company Chicago, Illinois. Copyright, 1918. Contained in a square wooden case, the test consists of a series of 11 color illustrations mounted on two plywood boards, representing a sequence of situations or events occurring during a day in the life of a boy. Each illustration contains a one inch square cutout. Each picture is to be completed by a selection of one of the 60 accompanying squares that would best complete the illustration. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 102 1237 Pictorial Completion Test -- II By William Healey Illustrated by Marguerite Davis. Published and manufactured by Stoelting Company Chicago, Illinois. 1964.A reproduction of the above, and contained in a square cardboard box, the test consists of a series of 11 color illustrations mounted on two plywood boards, representing a sequence of situations or events occurring during a day in the life of a boy. Each illustration contains a one-inch square cutout. Each picture is to be completed by a selection of one of the 60 accompanying squares that would best complete the illustration. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 102 1238 Pictorial Completion Test Illustrated by E. Manierre. Published and manufactured by Stoelting Company Chicago, Illinois, ca. 1930. Contained in a wooden case, the test consists of a large illustration mounted on a plywood board. The illustration depicts ten scenes in which various activities are being depicted. There are ten one square inch cut outs adjacent to each scene Each scene is to be completed by a selection of one of the 50 accompanying squares that would best complete the illustration. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 102 1239 Psycho-Diagnostic Puzzles Two wood block puzzles manufactured by the Stoelting Company Chicago, Illinois. Both are uncolored and unfinished plywood boards that have cut out shapes. One has exclusively rectangles, triangles and a square, while the other has circular pieces. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Box 102 1240 Bellvue Intelligence Test Manufactured by the Psychological Corporation, New York. ca 1940s Consists of six parts contained in separate boxes. Three are wood puzzles of a human face profile, a human hand, and a mannequin. Two are picture cards, and one is a box of sixteen one cubic inch colored blocks arranged to make designs (known as the Kohs Block Design Test) There are also nine cards illustrating test patterns contained in this box of blocks. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997
- Box 102 1241 Kohs Block Design Test. Manufactured by the C. H. Stoelting Company Chicago, Illinois. Sixteen one cubic inch colored blocks with 18 cards illustrating test patterns. Also, a reprint of an article by S. C. Kohs entitled “The Block Design Tests undated and source not listed. Ca. 1920s Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997
- Box 102 1242 The Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory, Minneapolis: University of Minnesota Press, 1942. Contained in a box, the test consists of approximately 350 cards containing statments in which the person being analyzed is supposed to classify as being “true,” “false,” or “cannot say.” Note that the following items belonged to Virginia Kirk. See biographical file for more information about her. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997
- Box 102 1243 Pseudo-Isochromatic Plates for Testing Color Perception. American Optical Company, Beck Engraving Company, 1940. Test used to determine color blindness. Note that the following items belonged to Virginia Kirk. See biographical file for more information about her. Donated by Dr. Warren Webb, January 24, 1997.
- Shelf 25 1244 Vanderbilt University Hospital, Surgery House Staff. Framed and photograph of the Surgery House Staff. Inscribed “To the Chief (Barney Brooks) From His House Staff December 17, 1943,” and signed by them. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1245 Vanderbilt University Medical Center. Framed aerial view of Vanderbilt University Medical Center, circa 1985 (frame is 13" x 15"). Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1246 Vanderbilt University Medical Center. Framed aerial view of Vanderbilt University Medical Center, circa 1989 (frame is 12" x 14"). Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1247 Vanderbilt University Medical Center. Framed aerial view of Vanderbilt University Medical Center. circa 1992 (frame is 20" x 26"). Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1248 Scott, Henry William, Jr., M.D. Framed pen and ink portrait of Dr. H. William Scott Jr., by Leon Schlossberg. Oval portrait is surrounded by sketches of the seals of the University of North Carolina, Harvard, Johns Hopkins, and Vanderbilt. Circa 1955. Water damaged at bottom. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1249 Schlossberg, Leon. Framed pen and ink wash illustration of the heart by Leon Schlossberg for a journal article by Dr. Scott. Circa 1952. Published in Journal of Thoracic Surgery, figure 5 volume 25 pages 26-39, January 1953. See back of frame for complete citation and description. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1250 Schlossberg, Leon. Framed pen and ink illustration of the esophagus by Leon Schlossberg for a journal article by Dr. Scott. Circa 1949. Published in Annals of Surgery, Volume 131, pages 186-193, 1950. See back of frame for complete citation. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1251 Schlossberg, Leon. Framed pen and ink illustration of the esophagus by Leon Schlossberg for a journal article by Dr. Scott. Circa 1949. Published in Annals of Surgery, Volume 131, pages 186-193, 1950. See back of frame for complete citation. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Shelf 25 1252 Schlossberg, Leon. Framed pen and ink illustration of the esophagus by Leon Schlossberg for a journal article by Dr. Scott. Circa 1949. Published in Annals of Surgery, Volume 131, pages 186-193, 1950. See back of frame for complete citation. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997.
- Shelf 25 1253 Schlossberg, Leon. Framed pen and ink illustration by Leon Schlossberg illustrating the management of a massive hemorrhage from renal pedicle after nephrectomy for a journal article by Dr. Scott. Circa 1949. Published in Journal of Urology, Volume 69, pages 26-31, 1953. See back of frame for complete citation. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Box 31 1254 Colostomy Saf-T Pouch. Colostomy Saf-T Pouch manufactured by the Marsan Mfg. Company, circa 1964. Sent as a sample to the Department of Surgery. Contains literature about this device as well as other similar products. Donated by Dr. H. William Scott, Jr. July 14, 1997
- Map case drawer 7 1255 Robinson Roscoe R. Certificate of appreciation from the Medical Board of Vanderbilt University presented to Roscoe R. Robinson on June 27, 1997 in recognition of his service to Vanderbilt. Signed by Edward Nelson, Chairman of the Medical Center Board, and Joe B. Wyatt, Chancellor of Vanderbilt University. Transferred from Vanderbilt News and Public Affairs (Gladys Smith), August 1997.
- Shelf 25 1256 Medical Library Association Framed hand-calligraphy certificate of appreciation from the Medical Library Association certifying that the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Library has met the requirements of the MLA and is approved to give internships in medical librarianship. Dated June 15, 1953. Transferred from Vanderilt Medical Library, 1997.
- Shelf 23 1257 Osler, Sir William. Framed contemporary (1984) charcoal portrait by Isabel Rath of William Osler representing him during his years at McGill University (ca 1880). Donated by The family of Dykes Cordell, August 28, 1997.
- Shelf 1258 Cadaver Ball. 1980 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1259 Cadaver Ball. 1985 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1260 Cadaver Ball. 1986 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1261 Cadaver Ball. 1987 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1262 Cadaver Ball. 1989 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1263 Cadaver Ball. 1990 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1264 Cadaver Ball. 1991 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1265 Cadaver Ball. 1992 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1266 Cadaver Ball. 1993 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1267 Cadaver Ball. 1994 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1268 Cadaver Ball. 1995 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1269 Cadaver Ball. 1996 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1270 Cadaver Ball. 1997 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1271 Cadaver Ball. 2000 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1272 Class Day 1991 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Class Day Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Shelf 1273 Cadaver Ball. 1988 Framed composite of photographs taken and the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine Cadaver Ball. Transferred by Vanderbilt Medical School (Janelle Owens), June 30, 2005.
- Box 103 1274 Medical Library Association Medal Silver and Bronze colored limited edition medals commemorating the 75th Annual Meeting of the Medical Library Assocation. Contained in black case. Inventoried May 28, 2010 (previously located in the safe)
- Safe Frances Lynch Office 1275 2009 10th International Congress of Medical Librarianship Commemorative Medal Gold plated bronze circular medal 70mm diameter and 5mm in thickness and contained in black case. Presented to Dr. Nunzia B. Giuse as a delegate to the congress, held in Brisbane Australia August 31 to September 4, 2009. A descriptive flyer is contained in the biographical file of Dr. Giuse. Inventoried December 8, 2010
- 1276 St. Bartholomew’s Hospital Framed engraving by G. Vertue entitled “View of St. Bartholomew’s Hospital” First published 1738 b in "A New and Universal History, Description, and Survey of The Cities of London and Westminster. Inventoried May 3, 2018
- 1277 Sydenham, Thomas Framed copperplate engraving by Jacobus Houbraken of English physician Thomas Sydenham. Published by J & P Knaptoton, London 1746 Inventoried May 3, 2018
- 1278 Garth, Samuel Framed copperplate engraving by Jacobus Houbraken of English physician Samuel Garth. Published by J & P Knaptoton, London 1748 Inventoried May 3, 2018
- 1279 Willis, Thomas Framed copperplate engraving by G Vertue of English physician Thomas Willis. Published by J & P Knaptoton, London 1742. Inventoried May 3, 2018
- 1280 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Metallic Tractors by James Gillray. Published in 1801 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1281 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Breathing a Vein by James Gillray. Published in 1804 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1282 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Comfort to the Corns by James Gillray. Published in 1800 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1283 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Taking Physick by James Gillray. Published in 1800 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1284 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Charming Well Again by James Gillray. Published in 1804 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1285 Guy’s Hospital Framed engraving of Guy’s Hospital, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1286 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Gentle Emetic by James Gillray. Published in 1800 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1287 Gillray, James Framed hand-colored aquatint caricature print entitled Brisk- Cathartic by James Gillray. Published in 1804 by H. Humphrey St. James's Street, London. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1288 Browne, Thomas. Framed copperplate engraving of Sir. Thomas Browne by Frederick Hendrik van Hove. Published in 1672. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1289 Harvey, William Framed copperplate engraving of William Harvey, MD William Harvey by Jacobus Houbraken after original portrait by Wilhelm von Bemmel 1739. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1290 Boyle, Robert. Framed copperplate engraving of Robert Boyle by George Vertue Published by J & P Knapton, London 1740. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1291 (London) College of Physicians Hand Colored etching and aquatint of the College of Physicians in London by Thomas Rowlandson and Auguste Charles Pugin, 1808. Inventoried October 9, 2018. Donated by Joseph M. Merrill.
- 1292 Bedpan Bedpan “Menicke” brand white porcelain Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1293 Bedpan. Slipper bed pan, English ironstone with instructions. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1294 Bedpan, Infant. Infant bed pan, white porcelain. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1295 Urinal. Urinal, male, white porcelain. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1296 Urinal. Urinal, female, white porcelain. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1297 Bedpan, Pediatric. Pediatric bedpan white porcelain. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1298 Bedpan. Bennington glaze stoneware bedpan. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1299 Respirometer. Wright’s respirometer contained in black case. 20th century Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1300 Inhaler. Dr. Nelson’s improved Inhaler, white porcelain with printed instructions. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1301 Chamber Pot. Wedgewood chamber pot White with black transferware pattern. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1302 Spittoon. Bennington glaze spittoon. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1303 Spittoon. Spittoon, small white porcelain with chicken faced spout. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1304 Invalid feeder. Invalid feeder round Staffordshire soft paste. White with blue transferware pattern. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1305 Nose douche. Nose douche white porcelain. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1306 Nasal douche. Nasal douche “Iglodine” brand Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1307 Medicine Spoon. Graduated medicine spoon, white porcelain. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1308 Medicine Spoon. Graduated medicine spoon, white porcelain S. Mawson and Thompson, London. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1309 Invalid Spoon. Small invalid spoon, porcelain with floral pattern. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1310 Medicine Spoon. Measuring dose spoon manufactured for “Harned’s Drugs.” Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1311 Invalid Spoon. Sheffield Silver plate invalid spoon with wooden handle. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1312 Infant Feeder. Small glass tube infant dripper feeder. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1313 Chloroform bottle. Chloroform dripping bottle, amber glass with graduated measuring marks. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1314 Vaporizer Lamp. Small “Vapo Cresolene” brand kerosene medicine vaporizer lamp. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1315 Specimen Tin. Parke Davis Company specimen tin. Orange colored with oval glass lid. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1316 Patent Medicine. “Lydia E. Pinkham’s Vegetable Compound” tablets in box. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1317 Patent Medicine. “Humphrey’s Homeopathic Preparation No. 34” for Throat Irritation contained in sealed box. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1318 Patent Medicine. “Vegetans Vegetable Laxative” pills in bottle contained in box. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1319 Patent Medicine. “Aerophagyl” in sealed tin container. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1320 Patent Medicine. “Gold Medal” compound pills contained in red tin container. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1321 Patent Medicine. “Mansfield Capillaris” medicine contained in bottle. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1322 Patent Medicine. “Bovinine Beef Tonic” contained in amber glass bottle. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1323 Patent Medicine. “Father John’s Medicine Tonic” contained amber glass bottle. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1324 Patent Medicine. “Stringer’s pulmonic Syrup” for coughs and colds contained in bottle and box. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1325 Dripper Bottle. 5.75-inch amber dripper bottle marked “T.K.” on the side and “100” on the bottom Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1326 Dripper Bottle. 3.5-inch amber dripper bottle marked “T.K.” on the side and “10” on the bottom.. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1327 Dripper Bottle. 4.5-inch amber dripper bottle marked “Lamprecht L-H” on the side and “50” on the bottom. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1328 Specimen Jar? Three-piece white ceramic jar marked “SENF” on the top and “Bauscher Weiden D.R.P” on the bottom. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1329 Invalid Feeder. White porcelain bird-shaped invalid feeder with handle. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1330 Baby Bottle. Clear glass graduated 8-ounce bottle, identified as baby bottle, with “124” on the bottom. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1331 Inhaler. White porcelain inhaler with mouth and nose holes, unmarked. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1332 Eye Wash Bottle. Blue glass eye-wash bottle with attached eye-cup stopper Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1333 Invalid Feeder. Painted 3.5-inch diameter invalid feeder marked “Bolton & Fairhead 1932” on paper taped to the bottom. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1334 Invalid Feeder. Blue and white porcelain invalid feeder marked “Germany 1733” on bottom 1334 Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1335 Invalid Feeder. Blue and white porcelain invalid feeder marked “WT&C” on the bottom. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.
- 1336 Invalid Feeder. Large black and white porcelain invalid feeder marked “Royal Doulton, England” on the bottom. Inventoried October 10, 2018. Donated by Joanne Lagerson, Sept 20, 2018.